Let's know the details of the top stocks from our colleagues Neeraj
and RV. Good morning to both of you.
Neeraj, which stocks will be the focus today?
Good morning and especially today, let's
talk about the results that have come. We have seen
important results coming from IC Lombard
and the results are quite good.
Look, especially the profit has
increased by 7% from here. There is an increase of about 17% in gross premium.
Operating profit has increased by 31% from here to stand
at 546 crores
.  The combined ratio has been seen to remain at almost 101.12%
and underwriting
losses, in particular, have been seen to increase slightly from here
.  It has increased to 282 crores against a loss of 209 crores,
so it is worth keeping an eye on it. The
overall results from here are
not disappointing
.  And especially look at the estimates for FY 27-28,
which have been slightly increased by the brokerage.
Looking at the results,
Goldman Sachs is currently giving a neutral view and is
giving a target of 1965.
They are specifically saying that good growth has been seen here
due to the health segment and the motor segment.
So
HSBC is also offering 2200 with a buy call,
which means that a
good growth can be seen in FY27 as well. Considering the improvement seen in the
premium and combined ratio at present, it is
expected that good results will continue in the coming time as well. So
keep an eye on ACI Lobard today, we can see some positivity
here.  Apart from this, the recently
listed company HDFC HDb Financials is to be
kept under observation.  Good results have
also been seen coming from HDB Financial.
Profits have since increased by 41% on a year-on-year basis.  On
the other hand, we have seen a 21.6% 6% increase in NI,
so we are seeing particularly
good results in the topline. On
the other hand, if you
look at loan losses and provisions, you have seen an increase of 8%, which is
a bit
worrying on a year-on-year basis. But if you
look at assets under management, it has
increased by about 10%, from 1.7 lakh crore
to 1.19 lakh crore, and the gross loan book has also
increased by 10% to 1.18 lakh crore,
so you are seeing a good growth
overall in loans within AUM
.  No Doubt Board has
also approved fund raising of Rs 32,824 crore through debt securities
.  We will see how the funds are raised,
but ADB Financials
is a company that has been listed for some time now, but
we have seen good improvement in the results of Atlist Q4
.  NIMS has made significant improvements
here, and with that, you may
see a positivity here today,
so you should pay attention to that.
Tejas Network also announced its results here
and the company's losses are seen increasing.
Last year, there was a loss of about 71 crores in this quarter,
which has increased to a loss of 211 crores
.  There is a pressure of 82% within the revenue
.  Revenue is being seen from here at 332 crores,
so there
is a huge decline in revenue and also look at the EBITDA loss. There was a
profit of 121 crores in the last quarter, against which
we are seeing an EBITDA loss of 118 crores coming from here
.  There are weak results,
weak execution, weak order book, and all of that, and a
lot of pressure is possible from here, especially within Tejas Network, these days.  A
while ago, we saw some buying coming in from a little lower inside this counter,
but now it doesn't seem like there's going to be any really good bullish
momentum here today,
so we'll have to keep an eye on it.  That's it, let's talk about the
results, now let's keep in mind the Q4
update of GMR Airport today
.  Traffic here has
increased by 0.9% to 9%,
we have seen a year-on-year increase of 32 million. In
addition, you have seen a domestic
traffic of 3.18 crores, which has
increased by 0.9%, and domestic
passenger traffic has increased by 1.6%.
So, the
overall figures are good. Obviously, the
international traffic has been
affected a little bit, as we have seen in March,
but the local growth is good, so we should pay
special attention to it. Although
the numbers are not very good, we
cannot expect any big growth today,
so we will keep an eye on it.  Now yesterday
when we saw the block deal of delivery in the pre-open session, we
discussed
that the details of this will come to us. Look, especially in
yesterday's block deal, Nexus Fund
sold 40 lakh shares at a price of 465 for 186 crores and especially against what Nexus Fund
sold, Morgan Stanley
Edelweiss Mutual Fund, Goldman Sachs,
Nippon India, Verdian Asia
Opportunity Fund, all of them have bought here
within the delivery, so keep an eye on that too.
Hearing the names of all these new buyers today,
we may see some increase in buying, so we will
definitely keep an eye on it. Finally, Aurobindo
Pharma is to be careful from here. From here, its
subsidiaries have
extended their agreements with Merck Sharp and Dom. There was a CMO pact, which was especially an
agreement to build a 60 kiloliter biological facility.  It has been seen to be extending from here,
so that will also have a positive impact
.  There won't be a huge positive impact,
but the news is good, so we
will also keep an eye on Aurobindo Pharma, but
all the results have come today.  Icici Lombard
HDAC HDB Financials will have a special focus on it
.  But apart from this, Aarti, there are many important
stocks in particular,
which are also to be kept in focus by many counters. Let's
start with RC here,
some news is coming here regarding the management,
where Rajesh Kumar has been
appointed as CFO and Director Finance from here and
he has been appointed from here from 2 April 2026,
due to which the focus is to be
kept on the counter of RC. Here, we will keep an
eye on how the stock reacts
.  The next counter
is the counter of Fino Payments Bank. News of investment has been
seen coming where the bank has
invested 200 crores in FinacleCBS migration and this investment has been made from here with the aim of
becoming a major bank from a small finance bank.
Along with this, the bank will be able to provide facilities like loans and fixed deposits from here in the future, which is what it has now,
so it is important to keep an eye on
Fino Payments Bank. There is a lot of positive news
here too, a reaction in the stock can be
seen moving towards a bullish trend.  Next
Counter is a counter of Surat Estate Developers
.  There is positive news here too
for the company. The company has acquired new land in the Dadar area of ​​Mumbai
and the
growth development value of the project is expected to be around Rs 100 crore
.  Along with this, there is a
possibility of a residential project being
developed here and the project
will strengthen the company's hold on premium locations like Dadar from here, so one should
also keep an eye on the counter of Suraj Estate,
a positive action can be seen moving forward here too
.  The next counter is the
counter of JGHV Infra.  The
company has received a contract from APCO Infratech
and a contract worth around Rs 815 crore has been
received from here, so
one thing to keep in mind here too.  The Next
Brigade Group is to be kept in focus because there are
reports of a joint development agreement being signed here.
Joint development agreements have been signed in Bangalore
and
these agreements have been signed for a gross development value of about 7200 crores.  The
agreement for the 8.63 acre land parcel has been signed, so the overall
brigade group side has to keep it in one focus from here today
.  Next Container
Corporation's counter is here.
News of receiving orders has been seen coming here.
The company has received an order from Braithwaite & Company. An
order worth about Rs 175.36 crore is being seen from
here. So,
on one counter, Concor's counter
can also be seen moving forward. Here, we have to keep an eye on it. And
finally, if we talk about Alcargo Terminals,
business updates are coming here. In
the month of March, we are seeing a 4% increase in total volume on a
year-on-year basis. And
if we talk about it on a month-on-month basis,
we have seen an increase of almost 2%.
So, due to good business updates, we
also have to keep a focus on the Alcargo Terminals counter. So,
many counters of tea,
which Neeraj mentioned, will all be in focus today
.  We will focus on the stocks that are going up,
but with patience and hard work.